<resources>
    <string name="app_name">觉浅</string>

    <string name="title_dialog_tips">提示</string>
    <string name="text_homepage">讨论</string>
    <string name="text_discovery">发现</string>
    <string name="text_ganhuo">干货</string>
    <string name="text_me">我</string>
    <string name="text_signout">注销</string>
    <string name="text_mymessage">我的消息</string>
    <string name="text_mycollection">我的收藏</string>
    <string name="text_myanswer">我的回答</string>
    <string name="text_recentlook">最近浏览</string>
    <string name="text_myquestions">我的问题</string>
    <string name="text_settings">个人设置</string>
    <string name="text_cleancache">清除缓存</string>
    <string name="text_aboutme">关于我们</string>
    <string name="text_aboutme_line1">©星空学生创新中心</string>
    <string name="text_aboutme_line2">www.xingkong.us</string>
    <string name="text_loaddata_again">点击重新加载</string>
    <string name="menu_allmessage">全部消息</string>

    <string-array name="tab_title">
        <item>论坛</item>
        <item>干货</item>
        <item>我</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tab_reals">
        <item>热门</item>
        <item>Android</item>
        <item>iOS</item>
        <item>前端</item>
        <item>拓展资源</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="text_press_again">再按一次退出觉浅</string>
    <string name="long_long_string">这是一篇很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长很长的文章</string>
</resources>
